

phone 816.547.7758

e-mail nickcopelin@gmail.com web

nickcopelin.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nickcopelin

# **Professional Summary**

Account Services and Client Engagement professional with 4+ years of success managing local and national clients in B2B and B2C relationships. Channel experience includes: digital, broadcast, radio, print, outdoor, direct mail, POP, SEM, and SEO.

### Education

Missouri State University, May 2011 College of Business - AACSB accredited Bachelor of Science in Marketing with an emphasis in Advertising and Promotions Minor in Design

#### Technical Proficiencies:

- · Microsoft Office Suite
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- · Google Business Applications GMail, Calendar, Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Slides
- Social Media Management and Measurement Tools Hootsuite and TweetDeck
- · Project Management Tools Basecamp, Trello, and Asana

# **Professional Experience**

#### Account Executive

Salva O'Renick; Kansas City, MO

October 2012 - Present

- · Serve as client's first point of contact in managing and executing projects
- · Assist Account Director in coordinating and producing special projects for clients
- Maintain weekly status reports and lead status meetings with clients and the agency
- · Participate in the preparation of materials for promotional planning and new business presentations as needed
- · Work in conjunction with creative and traffic to develop job estimates and timelines
- · Client experience: Applebee's, H&R Block, Ameriprise Financial, Central Bancompany, Missouri Employers Mutual, Lockton Companies, Protective Life Insurance, DST, GEHA, Charlie Histle

### **Account Coordinator**

July 2011 - May 2012

The Marlin Company; Springfield, MO

- · Assisted with various research projects
- · Routed projects internally
- · Populated and distributed insertion orders
- · Updated schedules and media calendars
- · Client experience: Starbucks, Bush Brothers Beans, Blue Bunny, Unilever, Splenda, and Sweet Street Desserts

## Internship Experience

Taco Bell Campus Marketing Representative

Williams/Crawford Marketing; Fort Smith, AR

- · Acted as liaison to15,000+ students
- · Coordinated sponsorships for organizations and campus-wide events
- · Set in motion numerous promotional deals, games, contests, and campaigns
- Developed, maintained, and utilized Facebook, Twitter, and Foursquare pages for promotional efforts

August 2010 - May 2011

phone 816.547.7758

e-mail nickcopelin@gmail.com

web nickcopelin.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nickcopelin

### Marketing Intern

May 2010 - August 2010

Breakthrough Marketing=Design+Technology; Kansas City, MO

- · Coordinated models, prepared inventory, and assisted in multiple photo shoots
- · Assisted with search engine optimization and Google AdWords campaigns
- Designed and populated template websites using NetworkSolutions.com and GoDaddy.com
- · Proofread and edited two 80+ page catalogues

### VP of Publicity

July 2009 - May 2010

Student Activities Council of Missouri State; Springfield, MO

- Oversaw a 6 person executive board in charge of student programming and a \$262,000 budget
- Utilized an \$11,000 budget for planning events and SAC publicity
- Created innovative advertising schemes and promotions utilizing grass roots and guerilla marketing techniques
- · Directed a 15 person committee to create, implement, and distribute publicity

### **Core Competencies:**

- Account management
- · Project management
- · Oral and written communication
- Relationship management
- Organization
- · Social media
- · Content marketing
- · Process improvement
- · Multi-tasking
- · Attention to detail
- Problem solving
- · Herding cats